[Music]
Downtown retail apocalypse. City
policies contradict. Walgreens closing
one by one. Target locks up everything.
Smash and grab. It's all the rage.
Organized theft takes center stage.
Billionaire tax breaks about mom and pop
shops hit the ground. Progressive
politics, progressive results. Urban
planning built on false cults. The city
by the bay of disarray as businesses
continue to fade away. Empty storefronts
line the streets. Tempolism in retreat.
Corporate chains are running scared
while city hall just stands it stairs.
By fun.
Watch them go
by.
Told you so.
[Music]
Security guards with hands all tied. The
shoplifterss run outside fight finger
discount daily thrill where consequences
equal nail techs pay grand for rent
while small shops can't make a dent
economic paradox to Francisco's
Pandora's box highrise towers boarded
doors what the hell are we fighting for
social experiment gone wrong that's the
theme of this damn song empty store line
the streets capitalism in the tree
Running scared while city hall just
stands in stairs
by by
watch them go
by.
[Music]
[Applause]